Register of the Georgie Anne Geyer Papers, 1944-1996
Hoover Institution Archives
- Notes for Guerrilla Prince, 1944-1987 (Box 14.-16.)
  - 72. Other books. Includes printed matter and interviews with Enrique Llaca and Angel Pino, 1986-1987. SEE ALSO: INTERVIEWS/Szulc, Tad (Folder 13)
  - 75. Venezuela. Includes printed matter and interviews with Fausto Amador and Beatrice Rangel, 1961-1987 (Folder 14)
  - 76. Fidel's personal life (Folder 15)
  - 78. Introduction. Includes printed matter, n.d. (Folder 16)
- Subject file, 1957-1989 (Box 17.-19.)
  Correspondence, notes, transcripts, memoranda, reports, newsletters, writings by others, press releases, biographical sketches, chronologies, and clippings and other printed matter. Arranged alphabetically by subject
  - General (Box 17.)
    - General. Printed matter, 1979 (Folder 1)
    - Chronologies, n.d. (Folder 2)
    - Conference and meeting matter, 1984-1987 (Folder 3)
    - Notes, 1985-1986 (Folder 4)
    - Writings by others
      - Betancourt, Ernesto. "Cuban Leadership After Castro," 1986. Typescript (Folder 5)
      - Cabrera Infante, Guillermo. "Suicide in Cuba," n.d. Typescript and printed excerpt (Folder 6)
      - Fillmore, Ann. "Affiliative and Bonding Behaviors: Valuable Insights into the Family," n.d. Mimeograph and notes (Folder 7)
      - Moses, Rafael. "The Leader and the Led: A Dyadic Relationship," 1987. Typescript and notes (Folder 8)
      - Packenham, Robert A. "Capitalist Dependency and Socialist Dependency: The Case of Cuba," 1985. Typescript (Folder 9)
  - Angola. Notes, chronologies, mimeograph copies of Jay Mallin, "Cuba in Angola," and Uniao Nacional para Independencia Total de Angola (UNITA), "UNITA: Daring to Challenge Soviet-Cuban Occupation in Angola," pamphlet, letter by Arnaud de Borchgrave, and printed matter, including an article by Gabriel Garcia Marquez, 1977-1988 (Folder 10)
  - Bay of Pigs invasion. Report, n.d. (Folder 11)
  - Batista, Fulgencio (Box 18.)
    - General. Notes and printed matter, n.d. (Folder 1)
    - Assassination attempt, 1957 March 13. Notes and printed matter, n.d. (Folder 2)
  - Castro, Fidel. Clippings, notes, printed matter, and a letter by Castro, 1965-1987 (Folder 3)
  - Chibas, Eduardo. Notes, n.d. (Folder 4)
  - Cleaver, Eldridge. Clipping and a letter by Jim Pringle, 1986 (Folder 5)
  - Colombia. Interview notes primarily relating to narcotics and guerrillas, 1986 (Folder 6)
  - Cuba
    - General. Report, notes, and printed matter, 1966-1989 (Folder 7)
    - Foreign relations. Memorandum, report, newsletter, interview excerpt, printed matter, and letters by Willy Brandt, Martin Kriele, and Felipe Pazos, 1966-1989 (Folder 8)
    - Rectification campaign. Mimeographed report, notes, and printed matter, 1984-1989 (Folder 9)
  - El Salvador. Printed article, 1985 (Folder 10)
  - Garcia Marquez, Gabriel. Printed matter, 1981-1982 (Folder 11)
  - Grenada. Memorandum, press release, messages, reports, newsletter, and printed matter, 1979-1984 (Folder 12)
  - Guiteras, Antonio. Notes, n.d. (Folder 13)
  - Kennedy, John F., Assassination of. Notes, printed matter, book excerpts and letter to the editor by Andrew Moscovit, 1975-1989 (Folder 14)
  - Lorenz, Marie. Clippings, 1960-1975 (Folder 15)
  - Machado, Gerardo. Notes, n.d. (Folder 16)
  - Marti, Jose. Notes, interview excerpt, and printed matter, 1962-1985 (Folder 17)
  - Missile Crisis. Notes, interview excerpts, memorandum by Arthur Schlesinger, meeting transcripts, and printed matter, 1962-1989 (Folder 18)
  - Narcotics. Telegrams, clipping, and typescript copy of Ernesto Betancourt, "Behind Castro's Narcogate," 1989 (Folder 19)
  - Nicaragua. Interview with Beatrice Rangel and printed articles, 1985 (Folder 20)
  - Operation Mongoose. Printed matter, 1975-1988 (Folder 21)
  - Qaddafi, Muammar. Printed article, 1989 (Box 19., Folder 1)
  - Religion. Notes, interview excerpts, printed matter, and mimeograph copy of James Malone, "Report on the Visit of NCCB to the Conference of Cuba," 1985-1988 (Folder 2)
  - Savimbi, Jonas. Biographical sketch and press release, 1986-1988 (Folder 3)
  - Vesco, Robert. Interview excerpts and printed matter, 1984-1987 (Folder 4)
  - Weather Underground organization. Report, n.d. (Folder 5)
  - Wieland, William Arthur. Newsletter, clippings, hearing transcript, and typescripts by Sarah McClendon, 1961-1965 (Folder 6)
- Audiovisual file circa 1983-1987 (Box 20-28)
  Audiotape cassettes, videotape cassettes, and photographs
  - Audiotape cassettes (Box 20.)
    - General
      - General. Radio broadcasts, press conference, meeting of Nicaraguan Contra opposition, interviews with Fidel Castro, Rafael del Pino and others, relating to Cuba, Central America, and the events surrounding the assassination of Jorge Eliecer Gaitan in Colombia, circa 1983-1987 (Folder 1-7)
    - Anonymous and unidentified (Folder 8-12)
    - Abascal, Gerardo, 1985 (Folder 13)
    - Aguilar, Juan, n.d. (Folder 14)
    - Aguilar, Luis E., 1985 (Folder 15)
    - Alexander, William, 1985 (Folder 16)
    - Asencio, Lazaro, 1987 (Folder 17-18)
    - Baldizon Aviles, Jose, 1985 (Folder 19)
    - Barquin, Connie and Luis Fernandez, n.d. (Box 21., Folder 20)
    - Barquin, Ramon, 1985 (Folder 21)
    - Bastillo, Carlos, 1985 (Folder 22-23)
    - Bayo, Alberto, Jr., 1986 (Folder 24-25)
    - Belt, Guillermo and Jack Skelly, 1985 (Folder 26-27)
    - Benemelis, Juan, 1986 (Folder 28-29)
    - Beruff, Jorge, 1984 (Folder 30)
    - Betancourt, Ernesto, 1984 (Folder 31-32)
    - Bonilla Sosa, Victor, 1984 (Folder 33)
    - Burstein, Luis, 1985 (Folder 34)
    - Canpi (?), 1986 (Folder 35)
    - Carrillo, Justo, 1986 (Folder 36-37)
    - Casals, Hamlet, n.d. (Folder 38)
    - Castaneda, Carlos, n.d. (Box 22., Folder 39-40)
    - Chayet, Zack, n.d. (Folder 41)
    - Chibas, Raul, 1985 (Folder 42-43)
    - Cleaver, Eldridge, 1984 (Folder 44-45)
    - Correa, Mayin, 1985 (Folder 46)
    - Costa, Octavio, 1984 (Folder 47)
    - Custodio, Isabel, 1987 (Folder 48-49)
    - Dalmau, Alberto, 1985 (Folder 50)
    - Duarte, Pepe, 1985 (Folder 51)
    - Echerri, Vicente, 1985 (Folder 52-53)
    - Escalona, Hilda Felipe de, 1987 (Folder 54-55)
    - Facio, Gonzalo, 1985 (Folder 56)
    - Figueres, Jose 1985 (Folder 57)
    - Figuero, Julio, 1984 (Box 23., Folder 58-59)
    - Fouad, Hamdi, 1986 (Folder 60)
    - Francon (?), 1986 (Folder 61)
    - Franqui, Carlos, 1987 (Folder 62)
    - Gaitan, Gloria, 1986 (Folder 63)
    - Garcia, Orlando, 1986 July 24-25 (Folder 64-65)
      Use copy reference number: 91037_a_0002829
    - Ginjauma, Jose de Jesus, 1986 (Folder 66-67)
    - Gomez, Cesar, 1986 (Folder 68-71)
    - Gross, Narciso, 1986 (Folder 72)
    - Guede, Emilio, n.d. (Folder 73-74)
    - Heredia, Richard, 1985 (Folder 75-76)
    - Hernandez, Giordana and Rene Viera, 1985 (Box 24., Folder 77)
    - Izquierda, Jose Maria, 1985 (Folder 78)
    - Khisha, M., 1986 (Folder 79)
    - Lara, Armando, 1985 (Folder 80-81)
    - Larroque, Enrique, 1985 (Folder 82)
    - Lazarus, Wilfred, 1986 (Folder 83)
    - Lopez Castro, Esther, 1986 (Folder 84)
    - Malone, James, 1985 (Folder 85)
    - Martin, Rosa, 1985 (Folder 86)
    - Martinez, Alice, 1987 (Folder 87)
    - Martinez Araras, Raul, 1985 (Folder 88-89)
    - Martinez Corbala, Gonzalo, 1986 (Folder 90-91)
    - Matos, Huber, 1986 (Folder 92-94)
    - Mora, Victor, 1987 (Box 25., Folder 95-96)
    - Mori, Oscar, 1985 (Folder 97-100)
    - Ochoa, Emilio, 1985 (Folder 101-102)
    - Orlani, Antonio, 1985 (Folder 103)
    - Otafa, Julio, 1985 (Folder 104)
    - Padilla, Herberto, 1987 (Folder 105-106)
    - Pardo Llada, Jose, 1986 (Folder 107-108)
    - Pazos, Felipe, 1984 (Folder 109-110)
    - Perez Alamo, Dunny, 1987 (Folder 111)
    - Pino, Rafael del, 1986 (Folder 112)
    - Rasco, Jose Ignacio, 1985 (Folder 113)
    - Rie, Manuel, 1985 (Box 26., Folder 114)
    - Rivero Aguero, Andres, 1985 (Folder 115-117)
    - Rodriguez, Delfin, 1984 (Folder 118)
    - Rodriguez, Luis, 1986 (Folder 119-122)
    - Rodriguez, Pepin and Manolo, 1987 (Folder 123-124)
    - Rojo del Rio, Manuel, 1985 (Folder 125)
    - Roy, Sunil Kumar and M. Rasgotra, 1986 (Folder 126)
    - Royal, Bob, 1987 (Folder 127-129)
    - Sanchez Perez, Alberto, 1986 (Folder 130)
    - Sargen, Andres Nazario, 1985 (Folder 131-132)
    - Sargento Jese, Jesus de Martinez, 1985 (Box 27., Folder 133)
    - Savimbi, Jonas, 1986 (Folder 134)
    - Skelly, Jack, 1984 (Folder 135-140)
    - Soler, Eugenio, 1986 (Folder 141-142)
    - Soni, Ambika, 1986 (Folder 143)
    - Sterling, Marques, 1987 (Folder 144-145)
    - Tamargo, Agustin, 1985 (Folder 147)
    - Torrijos, Moises, 1985 (Folder 148-149)
    - Ungo (?), n.d. (Box 28., Folder 150)
    - Valle, Blanca del, 1987 (Folder 151)
    - Vega, Jaime, 1985 (Folder 152)
    - Viera, Bernardo, 1986 (Folder 153-154)
    - Wald, Karen, n.d. (Folder 155)
  - Videotape cassettes. Interview with Fidel Castro by Elvira vb Samper, n.d. (Folder 156-157)
  - Photographs, 1986 (Box 10.A-V)
    - 96 prints of locations in Mexico City, primarily street scenes and buildings, associated with Fidel Castro and Jose marti, 1986 (Folder A-C)
    - 2 prints of the Belen Jesuit School, Havana and Miami; 2 prints of the Huber Matos, Jr. family, 1986 (Folder C)